I want to see, I want to see, I want to see!
I'm Yuukika and Yuuna Suzuki.
Please come with me.
The Orisu Expedition.
What is it? Yuna.
Are you copying Hikaru? I'm Yuna Hatsuki.
I'm Yuna Hazuki.
Aren't you being mocked a lot?
It's okay to be angry.
Now, today we have these two.
You'll see them in the back.
Today's exploration is...
Let's enjoy the rear garden!
Yay!
Cammy!
I wanna stop! I'm so happy!
Every year, this Ilari Expedition introduces the rear garden at Ebean's,
This year, 2023 Rear Garden has started again.
This year's eBean's Rear Garden has an amazing menu!
What is it?
May I take a look?
This year they have crab!
It's called the Premium Plan, and if you order this plan, you get all-you-can-eat crab!
Isn't that great? All-you-can-eat crab without even coming to the rear garden!
You can't talk while you're drinking, can you? We're having a good time, but everyone's just eating crab.
Crabs are falling.
It's not a "falling down" contest, it's a "hogging" contest.
It's amazing! We'll have samgyeopsal, like we did last year.
Seafood and meat sushi.
We didn't have that much until last year.
If you order the premium plan, there are 70 kinds of food!
You can't eat enough!
It's all you can eat and drink!
Let's order this premium plan today and eat it while introducing it to those who are watching!
Yes!
So, let's order!
First of all...
Canny!
I thought we were going to order the premium plan?
Oh, that's right!
I'll have the premium plan!
Garlic shrimp, cheese ring...
Safarro chicken! Yes, please!
And tteokbokki.
There's something else we want to eat.
It's not included in the price.
But we'll order this too.
Beef tongue, please.
Beef halami, please.
And today's fried noodles, please.
I'll start with drinks.
It's amazing, isn't it? Like a bar!
It's fun!
What do you drink, Mr. Lung?
Lung, you drink...
Alcohol, right?
But you'd be crazy if you drank beer.
That's what you're worried about, isn't it?
I'm still trying to keep it under control.
You haven't lifted the ban on that kind of crazy.
It's not that crazy.
You can't drink?
What's that?
Can you drink or not?
You don't know much about it?
I don't know. I've never been drunk.
I've never been drunk.
I've never done this before.
What do you mean you've never done it before?
What do you mean you've never done it? You're talking about some kind of dangerous drug. I've never done it.
You don't say you've ever had a drink.
What did you put in this?
A sour plum sour.
Sour plum sour?
It's the middle of the day.
Yes, it's lunchtime.
You really can eat as much as you want.
This is fun.
We should all come back.
Yeah, we all used to come here.
We all came here once before, didn't we?
This beer garden?
Yes, that's right.
We've all been here before.
But we haven't been recently.
I'd love to go to a beer garden.
Wouldn't it be too much trouble for nine people to go out to eat?
No, we'll go there.
We're so close.
Dinner with 9 people and a lot of staff.Dinner with 9 people and lots of staff.
We went many times during the tour.
During the tour.
I was told something like that.
The staff said there were too many of us.
We had to split up.
I cried myself to sleep at Ladako.
You want to go with everyone?
I have to go with everyone.
At my age?
Don't say that.
Well, we've ordered.
Let's go enjoy the beer garden!
Yay!
Crab! Oh, my God! So many crabs!
Refill 10!
I'm so happy.
Cheers!
That's great!
Do you want a stain?
I love it!
Bon appétit!
I'm a little confused.
It's just what I want.
It's coming out!
Oh, my gosh!
Dip this in the crab soup.
Crab soup?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my gosh!
Bon appétit!
Is it good?
Yummy!
Yum!
Bon appétit!
Wow, it's big!
Yummy!
Delicious!
But don't you eat crab when you go to Hokkaido on tour?
I did.
It was 10,000 yen for the crab.
Wow!
The captains in the back seat.
I heard the captains in the back seat saying that they didn't want us to order crab.
But I wanted to eat it, so I had no choice but to order it.
I hid and asked the waiter to bring it to me in secret.
I ate it.
Was it ok? The price, at the checkout.
They didn't find out, right?
I thought it would be confusing since there were a lot of people there, so I paid around 10,000 yen.
I told the story to the MC at the concert.
That was the first time I got to know Duster.
After that, the captain told me that you guys were a perfect crime.
Rawlic shrimp.
Looks delicious!
So delicious!
Looks like it would go well with alcohol!
I wondered if I should drink beer.
But I decided not to drink beer because I get turned on when I drink beer.
I decided not to drink beer.
I'm going to belly dance.
You know this place?
Did you meet him there?
They think I know you.
Like I know you.
I'd like to cook some meat.
First of all, I'd like to order beef tongue.
We'll definitely order beef tongue, won't we?
Thank you.
Is this attached to the house?
No, it's not.
You just put it there.
From cold to cold.
You're not going to an all-you-can-eat place, are you?
All-you-can-eat?
You can't eat it, can you?
What? No, we don't.
Do you go there?
Really?
You're the least likely to go.
I'm the furthest away.
In terms of image.
But I ate there once, about the fourth time in Northeast Japan.
I heard that before.
Fourth? That's very subtle.
You two just finished the tour.
How was it?
It was fun.
Junior high school?
It was tough, but fun.
That's nice.
I wish I could have gone around with you.I wanted to tour with them.
You can't tour in a normal life.
If I lived a normal life.
Touring.
When you say it like that.
I'm sure you're right.
But I've been here so long
I've been here so long that I don't realize that it's not normal.
I see.
What did you enjoy? On the tour.
The ramen I had in Hokkaido was delicious.
Shrimp ramen.
Hokkaido is really delicious, isn't it?
And Fukuoka is also delicious.
Mentaiko (cod roe) and so on.
What's the difference? Fukuoka's cod roe.
It was delicious because I ate it in Fukuoka.
It makes me feel like I'm in Fukuoka.
I feel like I'm in Fukuoka.
When you bring mentaiko from Miyagi to Fukuoka and eat it in Fukuoka, do you think it will be delicious?
And when you eat it in Fukuoka, you think it's delicious?
So-so, so-so.
If you eat it in Fukuoka...
The cold chicken was so good.
Cold chicken?
It's called Yumeyume Chicken.
It's a kind of seasoned bone-in chicken.
You don't heat it up.
They eat it cold.
I heard that Momoko-san eats it when she comes to Fukuoka.
I didn't know they had such a delicious dish.
It was really delicious.
I got it as a gift in my dressing room.
They were eating it after the concert.
They were eating it at the end of the show.
Everyone was biting into it at the end of the show? Chicken?
Me and the captain ate it first.
Why did the captain eat first?
It's margher, right?
He said, "This is a beer deal, isn't it?
I thought to myself, "This is definitely a beer thing.
So we hurriedly drank and ate together.
At the end of the concert?
I knew it was time to eat.
Bon appétit.
Is it good? I'm glad.
It's good.
Yes! Yes!
Yes! What is that?
Some kind of beef ribs.
When did you order that?
A lot of members say they can't eat any more ribs.
What?
Too oily.
Really?
Really!
You're not that old to have a sore liver.
It's called "belly meat".
Runchan is the oldest.
I love ribs.
It's fine.
You're just saying that.
You just want to say you can't eat kalbi, and act like an adult.
You don't get it, do you?
I'll say it next time.
What are you gonna say?
To everyone.
He said it's a secret ingredient, like kimchi.
He's the one with the slurpy mouth.
Everything tastes really good!
I'm sure it's good anywhere else.
Let's eat!
Eat up!
No, you didn't bake it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm doing it.
I feel like I want to do it for him.
I want to do it for you.
Even with friends.
Even when I'm with my friends.
I want to do things for them.
But my friends are really good at taking care of me.
They do everything for me.
And I was like...
I once told her that she was very good at taking care of me.
I told her that she was very good at taking care of me.
And he said, "I can't take care of them.I told him that I couldn't watch.
I was once told...
But you want to do it, don't you?
Because I want to do it.
I do it sometimes.
Because I sometimes fail.
I see.
Then it's better not to do it anymore.
Like, "Shut up.
I get that a lot.
But lately...
I can do it.
I've never seen you do it.
That's because you're dancing rough.
No, no, no.
No, really.
It's not good.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's not like we're doing it outside.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's a place for everyone to have fun.
Wait a minute... isn't it really good to dance rough?
I'll go get hot water.
I'm going to get some hot water.
Cross over, cross over.
You can say whatever you want.
He dropped a bomb and went away.
And then he ran away.
I'm not belly dancing.
It's good to be merry.
That's why I'm not belly dancing.
What are you into these days, Rune-chan?
What are you into?
I'm into some things.
When I'm talking to people, I don't want them to know.
I'm just...
What?
It's not that strong.
I'm addicted.
Are you putting it in today? Maybe.
Well, why don't you try it later today?
I'm sure we'll find out.
If he finds out about us, you've lost.
Something for Yuna, too.
Let's decide... together.
You know, it's okay for both of us to know.
We've decided... in our hearts.
If something doesn't feel right, it's just now, right?
It's okay to say so.
Make sure you put it in there at least once.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Hmm?
That was so thin.
What? Bare?
It's just what it is.
You know what I mean.
Oh, good.
I'll have the ham, please.
This time.
From this year, right?
Bon appétit.
What?
Yum! Yum!
The sauce is good!
The sauce on the ham!
It's so good! Highly recommended!
Highly recommended! Meat sushi!
Delicious!
Next is Yoo-chan's
Yoo-chan's?
What are we talking about all of a sudden?
I like the way she eats.
I like her face.
Let's talk about Harun-chan now.
Rune-chan can't cook barbecue.
She may not be your sister in that way.
But going out to eat together...
We've met a few times over the years, right?
And when we get into deep conversations, for example...
I feel like we've been living together for a year.
Really?
It's only a year, but it's a year.
It's not just the human world, you know.
I've also experienced the magical world.
I feel like the wizarding world can really help me with my problems in the human world.
I can count on you! That's cool!
But when I think about who I should talk to.
I think Hikaru would be the best person to talk to.I think it's best to talk to Hikaru.
Really?
You know what I mean?
He's going to tell me exactly what I need to know.
That's right!
You seem to know a lot of things.
Not only in what you say.
But first of all, she's very kind.
She doesn't deny what I've experienced or what I think.
What? Like that.
That's the best kind of attitude.
He's like "ahahahahaha" kind of attitude.
And they laugh.
And then he'll say, "I know how you feel.
Like, "Hikaru, you're like this, this, this, this...
Hikaru says, "Hikaru is like this, like this, like this...
He gives me his opinion from his own point of view.
I don't know...
I cough.
Why?
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Why did you get involved?
What's that?
Laughs
If you were to ask me for advice about something you've never experienced in your life...
I'm sure you'll be able to imagine it
She answers with that in mind.
I see.
I see. It's not that I don't understand because I've never had it happen before.
She doesn't say that.
Would you say something like, "If Hikaru were like that..."?
You should talk to Rune-chan about it.
So we got a lot!
It was delicious!
We ate crab this time.
We got this premium plan!
There were so many new items!
It was delicious!
Of course the crab was great!
The meat sushi was also delicious.
Above all, there are many menus to choose from!
There are so many to choose from!
It's really great!
It was so delicious!
I really want to come here with the whole group!
I really want to come again with the whole group!
I'm sure we will.
I hope you guys can come too!
I'd love to come.
If I see you...
I'll be drunk.
I don't know. I'm just talking.
I've only had one drink.
Start here.
You haven't had a drink.
Yes, I'd like to see you all
Have an ED.
Come to Sendai!
Next time, please try it!
Please do.
This open atmosphere is very nice and
Please come visit us and eat a lot if you can!
It's all you can eat and drink!
So today's experience was a paper project!
Did you read it yourself?
Please read it again.
Thank you very much.